Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- United Nations Fund for Population Activities Report for 1969-1972
  - United Nations Fund for Population Activities report for 1969-1972., AD_MC_093_ref45_000037_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.4 x17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - United Nations Fund for Population Activities report for 1969-1972., AD_MC_093_ref45_000038_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.4 x17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
- A letter from the Office of the Government of Abu Dhabi to Mohamed Habroush regarding H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's horses' races in London from Susan Sellons.
  - A letter from the Office of the Government of Abu Dhabi to Mohamed Habroush regarding H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's horses' races in London from Susan Sellons., 24 August 1971; AD_MC_093_ref46_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 29.8 x 20.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Arabic Writing; Medals/Insignia; London, England, UK; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Horses; Animals; Printed Materials
- A draft of a letter to King Faisal bin Abdulaziz Al Saud from H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan
  - A draft of a letter to King Faisal bin Abdulaziz Al Saud from H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan., Circa 1964-1975; AD_MC_093_ref47_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.4 x 20.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Arabic Writing; United Arab Emirates; Saudi Arabia; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents
- Correspondence Between H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and the Jordanese King
  - A telegraph translated onto paper from the king of Jordan to H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan wishing him good health., Circa 1965-1975; AD_MC_093_ref48_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 21 x 14.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Royalty; Presidents; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Jordan; United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing
- Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's Notebook Detailing Handwritten Notes, Maxims, and Translations of the Divine Comedy
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's notebook detailing handwritten notes, maxims, and translations of the Divine Comedy., 1932; AD_MC_093_ref50_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22 x 33 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's notebook detailing handwritten notes, maxims, and translations of the Divine Comedy., 1932; AD_MC_093_ref50_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22 x 33 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Arabic Calligraphy
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's notebook detailing handwritten notes, maxims, and translations of the Divine Comedy., 1932; AD_MC_093_ref50_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22 x 33 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Arabic Calligraphy; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's notebook detailing handwritten notes, maxims, and translations of the Divine Comedy., 1932; AD_MC_093_ref50_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22 x 33 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Arabic Writing; Printed Materials; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's notebook detailing handwritten notes, maxims, and translations of the Divine Comedy., 1932; AD_MC_093_ref50_000048_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22 x 33 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's notebook detailing handwritten notes, maxims, and translations of the Divine Comedy., 1932; AD_MC_093_ref50_000049_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22 x 33 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Arabic Writing; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Printed Materials
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's notebook detailing handwritten notes, maxims, and translations of the Divine Comedy., 1932; AD_MC_093_ref50_000050_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22 x 33 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's notebook detailing handwritten notes, maxims, and translations of the Divine Comedy., 1932; AD_MC_093_ref50_000051_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22 x 33 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Arabic Writing; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's notebook detailing handwritten notes, maxims, and translations of the Divine Comedy., 1932; AD_MC_093_ref50_000052_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22 x 33 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's notebook detailing handwritten notes, maxims, and translations of the Divine Comedy., 1932; AD_MC_093_ref50_000147_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22 x 33 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's notebook detailing handwritten notes, maxims, and translations of the Divine Comedy., 1932; AD_MC_093_ref50_000148_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22 x 33 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
- A letter from the London Office of the Government of Abu Dhabi regarding the order of three military suits for H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's three sons, Mohammed, Hazaa, and Hamdan
  - A letter from the London Office regarding the order of three military suits for H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's three sons, Mohammed, Hazaa, and Hamdan., 21 January 1972; AD_MC_093_ref51_0000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 22.1 x 16.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Arabic Writing; London, England, UK; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Printed Materials; Medals/Insignia
  - A letter from the London Office of the Government of Abu Dhabi regarding the order of three military suits for H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's three sons, Mohammed, Hazaa, and Hamdan., 21 January 1972; AD_MC_093_ref51_0000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17 x 21.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Arabic Writing; London, England, UK; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates
- H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's Driver's License Issued by the Government of Dubai
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's driver's license issued by the government of Dubai., 2 January 1959; AD_MC_093_ref52_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10 x 6.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's driver's license issued by the government of Dubai., 2 January 1959; AD_MC_093_ref52_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10 x 6.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Arabic Writing; English Writing; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's driver's license issued by the government of Dubai., 2 January 1959; AD_MC_093_ref52_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10 x 6.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's driver's license issued by the government of Dubai., 2 January 1959; AD_MC_093_ref52_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10 x 6.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's driver's license issued by the government of Dubai., 2 January 1959; AD_MC_093_ref52_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10 x 6.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's driver's license issued by the government of Dubai., 2 January 1959; AD_MC_093_ref52_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10 x 6.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Officials; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Printed Materials; Studio Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's driver's license issued by the government of Dubai., 2 January 1959; AD_MC_093_ref52_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 10 x 6.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
- PENDING REF 53
- H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's Passport Issued by the Government of Dubai
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's passport issued by the government of Dubai., 7 October 1969; AD_MC_093_ref54_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 15.5 x 10.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Arabic Writing; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Passport/ID card
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr's passport issued by the government of Dubai., 7 October 1969; AD_MC_093_ref54_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 15.5 x 10.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Arabic Writing; Men; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Passport/ID card; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; English Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's Passport Issued by the Government of Dubai
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's passport issued by the government of Dubai., 22 April 1957; AD_MC_093_ref55_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 15.5 x 10.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Arabic Writing; Printed Materials; Passport/ID card; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Humaid Bin Rashid Bishr's passport issued by the government of Dubai., 22 April 1957; AD_MC_093_ref55_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 15.5 x 10.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Printed Materials; Passport/ID card; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; English Writing